Hey y'all, just wanted to come on here and let you know if you hadn't figured this out yet, but
the Republicans are the oppositional party, not the Democrats. Like I think some of y'all think
that like the Republicans are like the America that's racist, that's discriminatory, that's
sexist, and like the Democrats are like fighting them to be like good Americans. But like America
was always racist, was always sexist, was always discriminatory. And the Democrats were
here for all of that. So they were already here being all those things. And then the
Republicans said, nah, we need to be more of those things. Y'all trying to give black people
rights? We're going to go even more right. And black people were brought on board because
the South became swing states. You follow me? The Democrats are the ones who were already
there. They were already here. Their opposition party is the Republicans. They're not an opposition
party. That's why they never do the opposition thing that folks think they're going to do.
So if you still believe in electoral politics and you listen to folks who say all of this,
like we need a complete reform of the Democratic Party. Well, check it. The definition of reform
is to make improvements. So if the Democratic Party fell off because it wasn't as racist as
the Republicans, then wouldn't it make sense in their minds that to improve would be to get back
to their old guard of racism? That's why you hear people like Bernie Sanders saying things like,
ah, the border is just too open. We have too many people coming through. And I mean, Nazi tattoo,
Nazi smash move. That was kind of Nixon, but you know what I mean? If the original formation
was already all about that slavery life, what are you reforming?
The United States government, as it has been known, is being destroyed in real time. Don't let them fool
you. It is crumbling. They're doing the work for us. So we need to have something better to put in
place on the other side. And in my opinion, that begins with parties formed through public servitude
and constituency services from the ground up, not the top down. Talk about yourselves. I'll see you
later. Head to amandaseals.com to get your tickets to the live stream performance and book release of
my latest work, What Would the Ancestors Say?